[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["11:45 Eastern"]}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "Dana, I take it they started the actual debate, the vote could be fairly soon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Well, they have started the debate on the procedural issues, but I just actually am getting an e-mail right now saying that the final vote, it doesn't look like it will happen until much later, until some time between 11:15 and 11:45 Eastern.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "If the majority is not there of the Republicans who are the majority in the House, he's not going to bring it up for a vote, or are they discarding that given this current crisis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "He's never been officially wedded to that majority of the majority idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "So there's a possibility that he might actually go before cameras and make a statement assuming it passes the House?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "They're not saying that, but he is -- he is here in the building, and this would be a victory.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "I take it there's no full lid, as they say, over in the West Wing at the White House, meaning that there's still a possibility that the TV crew are still there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "They are still there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "LOCATION": ["West Wing"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Congresswoman, you're going to vote which way for this Senate bill?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Hi, Wolf.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate", "Senate", "Senate", "White House"], "LOCATION": ["Wolf"], "PERSON": ["Reid"]}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Are you going to vote in favor of the Senate bill or are you going to vote against it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "I'm a very reluctant yes, Wolf, because under these circumstances which exist, this last-minute situation exists because the folks just back behind me in the Senate chamber, Senator Reid, could not get the Senate to act on any of the great bills for the American people we sent before, this is the best we can do given the Senate and the White House sentiment at this point in time.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Is that a correct assumption?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "I think that's probably a valid assumption, Wolf.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "And so you assume like I do that it will pass the House of Representatives, a bipartisan majority, more than 217 votes and it will go to the president for his signature perhaps as early as tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNPS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "That's what I anticipate, Wolf, and I certainly will be glad to get this particular issue settled and now it's on to tackling that hideous problem that we have and we owe it to the American people to do everything we can.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House of Representatives"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "LITZER: How many Democrats -- how many Democrats do you think will vote in favor of this Senate-passed version?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NNPS", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NNPS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Well, I think it's hard to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBZ", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "NN", "VBG", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "Do you have any doubt that this legislation will be passed tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Well, I'm pretty confident that the legislation is going to pass, what I'm hopeful is, really, actually anyone watching this, Wolf, should have just taken out some stock in Dramamine because the rollercoaster ride that has resulted from us getting to this process really has been unfortunate and unnecessary but we're here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "What do you say to those colleagues of yours who don't like this deal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Well, I'm a progressive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "But you agree, Grover, with Debbie Wasserman Schultz, if you were a member of the House or the Senate, you'd be voting for this legislation as well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House", "Senate"], "PERSON": ["Grover", "Debbie Wasserman Schultz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "But -- I just want to make sure -- I just want to point out, Grover Norquist, though, having said all that and everything you said, you are giving cover to those Republicans who will vote in favor of the Senate legislation in the next hour or two?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "RP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", ",", "VBG", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNPS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "They're not -- they're not voting for a tax increase, they're voting to save tax cuts for as many people as they can over Obama's objections.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"], "PERSON": ["Grover Norquist"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Yes, I assume you're in favor of this Senate-passed language?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Oh, I'm going to vote for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Is that the number you're hearing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Well, I'm interested in seeing how many votes the Republicans are going to provide.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNPS", "WP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "You say children, you're talking about the Speaker of the House and the Majority Leader?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "I'm talking about Tea Party Republicans who continue to throw temper tantrums and delay this and refuse to move forward in the spirit of compromise.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "You think the Republican leadership, the speaker, the majority leader, some of the other leaders, they're all on the same page or are they fighting amongst themselves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Oh, I think a good part of this has had nothing to do with an economic strategy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"], "LOCATION": ["New York"], "PERSON": ["Chuck Schumer"]}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Were you surprised the president was willing to go up to $450,000 from $250,000, which he had spoken of for months and months and months during the campaign?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "$", "CD", "IN", "$", "CD", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, I wasn't completely surprised because there are a lot of Democrats particularly in the Senate, particularly representing wealthy states like New York, Chuck Schumer, for example, who always kind of wanted that threshold to go up a bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$450,000", "$250,000"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "WP", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "God deal or bad deal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, I guess it depends on for who.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", ":", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Who is the big political winner tonight, Ben?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "I think President Obama played a much stronger hand and won with it in this sort of shoving match over -- particularly forcing Republicans to go ahead and raise taxes on the rich.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House"]}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Assuming it passes, Ben Smith, what do you think the future for John Boehner, the speaker, is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "I think he was just overheard on the floor of the House calling tonight a nightmare for him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Smith", "John Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Around 11:00, 11:15, that's when roll call will take place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "We just got a little bit of good news that it might happen in the 10:00 hour, a little bit earlier.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]